本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
悠着点  重力泉的人们
Watch out, Gravity Falls,
因为现在可是43度高温
Because at 110 degrees
我们正经历着这个夏天最最炎热的一天
we're looking at the hottest day of the summer!
赞成今天什么事儿也不做的  吱一声
All in favor of doing nothing all day, say...
我要把这只猪扔出屋去
I'm gonna throw this pig out of the house!
你知道我的底牌  臭猪
You called my bluff, pig.
而往好处看呢  这是意味深长的一语双关
On the bright side, pun very much intended,
现在是重力泉游泳池的开放周
It's opening week at the Gravity Falls pool.
重力泉游泳池
Gravity Falls pool?
-今天  -一语双关
- Today? - Pun intended?
快  都上车
Quick! To the car!
嘿  孩子们  帮一把
Hey, kids, a little help here.
好了  向泳池进发
All right, off to the pool.
还有要注意  天干物燥  小心野火
And remember to be on alert for random wildfires.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
他会没事儿的
He'll be fine.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
CC录制： ufohaman  Qin Cong
时间轴： sunshine
■
翻译： Chamania  不远景
校订： Enpistu  WaitinZ
■
后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第一季第十五集
Gravity Falls  S01E15  The Deep End
好啦  谁想来个水上炸弹
All right, who wants to do a cannonball?
发射
Cannonball!
啊  游泳池
Ah, the pool.
魅力夏天中的闪闪绿洲
Sparkling oasis of summer enchantment.
是啊  没什么比和陌生人坐在潮湿的浴缸里更享受了
Yeah, nothing like sitting in a moist tub with strangers.
就好像挤公交  不过这是湿的
It's like the bus, but wet.
为什么太阳还要戴太阳镜呢
Why would a sun need to wear sunglasses?
你还是别多想的好
It's best not to think about it.
喔喔  别讲话
Whoa, whoa! Stop the presses!
那是谁啊
Who's that?
哦  对了  据说那哥们儿从没离开过泳池
Oh, yeah. Word is, dude never leaves the pool.
人们都说他是“神秘的独行侠”
People say he's a "Mysterious loner."
这儿是不是变热了  还是那个家伙太帅了
Is it getting hot out here, or is it just that guy?
今儿可是今年最热的一天啊  梅宝
It's the hottest day of the year, Mabel.
还有  你就不能坚持一周
Besides, can't you go for one week
尽量不要疯狂地迷恋上陌生人吗
without having a new crush on some random guy?
这可不行
Uh-uh.
快看他的小胡须啊
Look at his little moustache hairs!
很明显你是一见钟情了  去追他吧
You are clearly enamored. Go to him.
-喂  干嘛呢  -看着点  小屁孩
- Hey, come on! - Watch it, kid!
哎呀  抱歉
Oops, sorry!
真是太美好了
It's so beautiful!
呃  梅宝就是说说而已  想听个秘密吗
Eh, Mabel's all talk. You wanna know a secret?
她以前从没亲过男生
She's never even kissed a guy before.
不知怎么的  她总会搞砸
She always messes it up somehow.
哎  女人啊
Oy, women!
嘿  派恩斯先生
Hey, Mr. Pines.
温蒂  救生员哪儿去了
Wendy? Where's the lifeguard?
我就是救生员啊
I am the lifeguard.
我来定规矩  笨蛋  砰
I make the rules, sucka! Boosh!
她用水袭击我
Aah! She's attacking me with water!
你在这儿工作
Wow. You work here?
我发现救生员有免费吃零食的好处
I found out lifeguards get free snack privileges.
而且  我的位置是这儿最好的
Plus, I get the best seat in the house.
是啊  那是自然的
Yeah, you do!
我傻笑得太久了
I've been laughing for too long.
伙计  你和温蒂在进行  秘密瞪眼比赛吗
Dude, are you and Wendy having a secret staring contest?
因为我觉得你要赢了
'cause I think you're winning--
苏斯  嘘
Soos! Shh!
那么  想不想再砸斯坦叔公几个水球呢
So, hey, you wanna go chuck more water balloons at grunkle Stan?
我超想啊  但是我今天还得负责选人工作
I'd love to, but I gotta spend the day doing tryouts.
我们正在找一个新的助理救生员
We're looking for a new assistant lifeguard.
嘿
Hey!
Hey...
让我来当那个助理救生员怎么样
What if I was assistant lifeguard?
那一定会超级好玩  就是你了  伙计
That would be so much fun! You're totally in, dude!
你只用先跟我的老板报到就行  普切克先生
You just have to check in with my boss first, Mr. Poolcheck.
你的老板
Your boss?
我要来抓你了
I'm gonna get you!
我的天  能在这儿撞见你真是太疯狂了
Wow! Oh, my gosh, how crazy, bumping into you here,
即使我们彼此还不认识
even though we don't know each other.
你在水底下待了多久啊
How long have you been underwater?
那不重要啦
That doesn't matter!
嗨  我叫梅宝
So, hey! My name's Mabel.
你好啊
Hola.
你是澳大利亚人吗
Whoa! Are you Australian?
你的幽默感真让我着迷
I am charmed by your sense of humor...
而且你不带游泳圈就下水真大胆
And your bold lack of water wings.
你真是太逗了
You're so funny!
还有  你的头发好赞
And your hair is beautiful.
哦  一点也不  有很多烦人的结
No, no, it has silly tangles.
能让我
Mind if I...
梅宝  你为什么这么有先见之明啊
Why, Mabel, you are so forward.
就是这样  他喜欢你
This is it! He likes you!
加油  梅宝  时机到了
Go for it, Mabel! It's time!
赶快约他去约会
Ask him out on a date!
那啥  想不想上去啊  我们可以去零食店或是
So, hey, you wanna go dry off? Maybe hit the snack bar or--
我恐怕不能去
I--I'm afraid I cannot.
因为我有个可怕的秘密
For I have a terrible secret!
我得走了
I must go.
真难过
I'm upset.
但是好想知道哦
Yet, intrigued.
那就是我认为自己可以胜任优秀助理救生员的原因
And that is why I think I'd make a good lifeguard assistant.
防晒指数100  棒极了  我喜欢你
Spf 100? Good. I like you.
但是这可不是个轻松的工作  这儿已经乱套了
But this isn't an easy job. It's anarchy out there.
我觉得我能应付得了
I think I can handle it.
你能应付这个吗
Can you handle this?!
一个泳池过滤器令我丢掉了一只手
I lost my hand to a pool filter!
游泳池表面上看起来很友好
The pool may seem friendly,
但是她能瞬间和你翻脸
But she can turn on you in an instant!
这就是为什么  你必须要尊重她的规则
Which is why you must respect her rules!
你认为自己具备这些条件吗  孩子  你行吗
Do you think you have what it takes, boy? Do you?!
当然  我想吧
Sure. I guess.
欢迎来到深水区  孩子
Welcome to the deep end, son.
谢谢了  我
Well, thanks. I--
是啊  这可不妙
Yep, oh, this is happening.
苏斯  这就是我的宝贝
There she is, Soos.
这里距离零食店和厕所一般近
Equidistant from the snack bar and the bathroom,
又有恰到好处的阳光和阴凉
Just the right amount of sun and shade.
并且离给自己擦乳液的老头子麦戈科特远远的
and pointed away from where old man Mcgucket lotions himself.
最完美的躺椅
The perfect lawn chair.
你在车里和我讲的传说是真的啊
The legends that you told me in the car were true.
我简直不敢相信这座还没被占
I just can't believe it wasn't already taken!
现在坐下来  向世界宣告这是我的位子
And now to sit on it, thereby claiming it as my own.
什么
What?!
你好啊  斯坦福
Why, hello, Stanford.
吉迪恩  快离开我的椅子  小屁孩
Gideon! Get out of my chair, kid!
我的天  这是你的椅子啊  我可不知道呢
Oh, my, was this your chair? I had no idea.
其实我知道的  斯坦  我清楚得很
Yes, I did, Stan. I knew.
滚开  你个小矮子
Move it, you little troll!
先到先得
First come, first serve!
让我先来好好伺候伺候你
I'll first serve you!
别这样  温蒂
Come on, Wendy!
你怎么能对一个老人这么做呢
You can't do this to an old man!
抱歉  斯坦  这可由不得我
Sorry, Stan. It's not up to me.
实际上  这就是由我决定
Actually, it is.
嘿  温蒂  我得到这份工作了
Hey, Wendy. I got this job!
太棒了  想去滥用一下咱们的权力吗
Sweet! Wanna go abuse our power?
但普切克逮住我们怎么办
But what if poolcheck catches us?
他好像情绪不太稳定啊
He seems emotionally unstable.
哎呀  不用担心的  伙计
Nah, don't worry, man.
你只要悄悄地破规矩就行
You just gotta be sneaky about your rule-breaking.
看谁先到“不准乱跑”的标志牌哪儿
Race you to the no running sign!
你进来得呆多久
How long you in for?
两个小时  因为打架斗殴
Two hours, for roughhousing.
但我是无辜的啊
But I'm innocent!
泳池监狱也不是那么糟糕啦
Pool jail ain't so bad...
只要你没被关单人禁闭
As long as you don't wind up in solitary.
黑夜总是最难熬的
It's the nights that are the hardest.
嗨  看过来
Hey, there!
我给你买了个三明治
I brought you a sandwich.
虽然有点湿了  但还是很好吃的
It's sort of wet, but it's still good. Blop.
我喜欢和别人分享东西  比方说三明治啦  秘密啦
I like sharing things-- sandwiches, secrets...
分享你的秘密吧  美丽的陌生人
Share your secret, beautiful stranger.
这个湿漉漉的三明治看起来真美味
That wet sandwich does look delicious.
那好吧
Oh, very well.
但是你绝对不能告诉别人我可怕的秘密
But you must never tell another living soul my terrible secret.
你得离我远点  因为我是
You have to stay away from me because I am...
一条人鱼
A merman.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank goodness.
我还以为你要说你已经有女朋友了呢
I thought you were gonna say you had a girlfriend.
一条人鱼
A merman! Ha!
我早就应该从你奇怪的异国鱼语当中听出来
I should have known from your strange foreign fish language.
那是西班牙语
It is spanish.
你的嗓音又低沉又有男人味  你多大了
Your voice is so deep and masculine. How old are you?
我十二岁了
I am 12 years old.
我们人鱼大概三岁的时候变声
Merman's voices change when we are, like, three.
那么你叫什么名字呢
So what's your name?
有一些人叫我
There are some who call me...
美男鱼
Mermando.
这是因为美男鱼是我的名字
This is because Mermando is my name.
但是我没明白  美男鱼
But I don't understand, Mermando.
像你这样的人鱼怎么会在公共泳池里呢
What's a guy like you doing in a public pool?
这是个忧伤的故事  梅宝
It is a tragic story, Mabel.
我本来在和我万能的海豚朋友畅游大海
I was swimming with my friends, the mighty dolphins,
但是在墨西哥湾时  我却落入渔网
In the gulf of mexico, when I was ensnared!
厄尔  我们是不是抓到了
Earl, did we just catch ourselves
某种美丽的人鱼啊
some kind of beautiful man-fish?
咱们来尽情享用他的美味吧
Let's feast on his flesh!
当货车向重力泉驶去的途中
The cargo was headed for gravity falls.
我用尽了全力试图逃回家
Using all my strength, I tried to escape back home,
可结果却没那么顺利
but it was not to be.
我差点就因脱水而死
I would have died of dehydration,
要不是森林里动物们的好心帮忙
were it not for the kindness of the forest animals.
继续舔
Continue licking! Oh!
但如今你知道我的真实身份
But now that you know what I am,
你肯定觉得我是个怪胎
you must be seriously weirded out.
怎么会  我才不会介意你是条人鱼
What?! I don't care that you're a merman!
你大概是  我见过最酷的家伙
You're, like, the coolest guy I've ever met.
而且你还能在吉他上弹出至少一个和弦呢
And you can play at least one chord on the guitar.
梅宝  我还从来没见过你这样的人类
Oh, Mabel. I have never met another human like you.
你愿意一起玩游戏  马可波罗吗
Would you care to join me in a game of the marco polo?
愿意  美男鱼  当然愿意
Oh, yes, Mermando! Yes!
你压着我的腮了  我快喘不过气了
You're covering my gills. I cannot breathe.
是有点奇怪了
Weird.
我的脸蛋像婴儿一样柔滑
Ooh! My cheeks are baby soft!
看看他自鸣得意的样子  抢我位子的混蛋
Look at him, that smug chair-stealing jerk!
但我又不能碰他
But I can't touch him,
不然泳池巡查又会把我丢进监狱的
or the pool patrol will throw me in pool jail.
就是这样  烧伤那个小屁孩
Yes. Yes! Burn the child!
我的眼睛
Aah! My eyes!
和我斗
Deal with it.
苏斯
Soos.
充气鸭子  是你吗
Inflatable duck guy? Is that you?
是的  苏斯  我会说话
Yes, Soos. I can talk.
我的天  我就知道你们暗地里是活着的  我就知道
Oh, my gosh, I knew you guys were secretly alive. I knew it!
嘘嘘  别出声
Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh!
我的人民正被奴役  苏斯  请你给我们自由
My people have been enslaved, Soos. You must free us.
充气鸭解放革命已经来临了
The inflatable pool duck revolution is at hand.
泳池关闭  清场了  各位
Pools closing! Clear out, everyone!
-普切克  -快躲起来
- Poolcheck! - Hide!
出去  别乱碰
Out! Do not touch!
助理救生员
Assistant lifeguard!
晚安  孩子  帮我把储藏间锁好
Have a good night, son. Lock up the supplies for me.
游泳池要关了
The pool, she closes.
我们今晚能见面吗
Can I see you tonight?
好啊  在哪里  想去散步吗
Sure. Where? Wanna go for a walk?
人鱼  我是条人鱼
Merman. I am a merman.
哦对  那我今晚过来好了
Oh, right. Then I'll be back tonight.
请勿触碰
请勿翻越
看啊  这是一本关于人类的贴图册
Look, here's a scrapbook of human stuff.
这是我用双腿站立
Here's me standing with my legs,
这是我在踢迪普的腿
And here I am kicking Dipper in his legs.
之后他的腿就动不了了
He couldn't move his legs after that.
你能想象没有腿会怎么样吗
Can you imagine, not having legs!
我们略过这段吧
Let's skip this part.
这是我们全家人在练踢拳
And here's my whole family kickboxing!
怎么啦
What's wrong?
我曾经也是有家人的
I, too, used to have a family once,
在海里的时候
Back in the ocean.
我好想念他们啊
How I miss them.
美男鱼  你为什么不离开游泳池呢
Mermando, why don't you just leave the pool?
我只尝试过一次
I tried only once.
但是逃出游泳池需要一个计划
But escaping this pool required a plan
一个大胆的计划
that was bold and daring.
然后狼也引来了
And then the wolves came.
不  我很高兴能在这里  因为我遇见了你
No, I am glad that I am here, because I met you.
就是现在了  梅宝
This is it, Mabel.
初吻时刻  就是现在了
First kiss moment, here we come.
勇往直前吧
Just go for it!
你的嘴怎么了
What are you doing with your mouth?
我么  没有  那个  我刚刚在吃酸糖
Me? Nothing! This? I was just eating some sour candy.
我的嘴唇会撅起来是因为糖太酸了
So my lips were doing that 'cause the candy was so sour.
能给我吃一块吗
Can I have some candy?
不行
No.
怎么
What the--
-我好害怕  -我也是
-I'm scared! -Me, too!
一百分
One hundred points!
伙计  有了这个工作
Dude, with this job,
咱们俩整个夏天都会超级快乐的
You and me are gonna be having fun all summer!
整个夏天
All summer?
派恩斯  过来  马上
Pines, here, now!
你向我保证过
You gave me your word that you
你会遵守这个市立游泳池神圣的规则
would respect the sacred rules of this municipal pool!
普切克先生  您在哭吗
Mr. Poolcheck, are you crying?
这种事现在无关紧要
That's not important right now!
你的处境很危险  小子  想保住你的工作吗
You are on thin ice, boy. You wanna keep this job?
好吧  某个神经病昨天晚上闯进了游泳池
Well, some maniac broke into the supply closet last night
而且还弄坏了我们唯一的网勺
And destroyed our one and only pool skimmer!
我要你监视这里
I want you on a stake out.
如果再有任何一件东西被偷  我就解雇你
If one more supply gets taken, you're fired!
我不会让您失望的
I won't let you down!
美男鱼  准备好  我要出手了
Mermando, get ready! I'm gonna bring the heat!
美男鱼  你还好吗
Mermando, are you okay?
哦  是你的家人对吧  你在想他们吗
Oh, it's your family, isn't it? Are you thinking about them?
美男鱼  够了
Mermando, enough is enough!
我实在太喜欢你  看不得你如此失落的样子
I care about you too much to see you like this.
我要帮你逃出去让你和家人团圆
We're gonna bust you out of here and get you back to your family.
但是  梅宝  想要逃脱是不可能的
But, Mabel, escape is impossible!
我们今晚就帮你逃出这里
We're breaking you out of here tonight!
哦  水  抱歉
Whoops! Sorry about that. Water.
好了  迪普  计划是这样的
All right, Dipper, here's the plan.
抓住入侵者  保护好公物
Catch the trespasser, protect the supplies,
保住在泳池的工作  最终和温蒂结婚
Keep job at pool, and eventually marry Wendy.
不许动
Freeze!
斯坦叔公
Grunkle Stan?
我  呃  在梦游
I, uh, I'm sleepwalking.
然后  现在在说梦话
Also, now I'm sleep-talking.
顺便说一句  帽子很好看啊
Nice hat, by the way.
你  你就是毁坏泳池公物的家伙
You! You're the one destroying pool supplies!
什么  不是  我要做的坏事比那个高级得多
What? No! My crime is a lot better than that.
我要占据那个座位
I'm gonna get that seat,
在吉迪恩早上来之前准备好
and be ready in the morning when Gideon comes.
或许在这之后我可以再弄坏点泳池用品  才刚入夜啊
Then maybe I'll destroy some pool supplies. Night's still young.
小声点  好啦  我这就走
Sheesh, all right, I'm going!
嘿
Hey!
梅宝
Mabel!
你准备好去见家人了吗
Are you ready to see your family?
当然  可是  怎么逃  我是条人鱼啊
Yes, but how can I, a merman, possibly escape?
好吧  我原先的计划是把几个鱼叉绑在一起
Okay, my original plan was to tape together a bunch fish sticks
给你做一双仿真假腿
to make you a prosthetic pair of people legs.
有趣啊
Intriguing.
不过之后我意识到
But then I realized that
我只要用这个冷藏箱来运输你就好了
I could just transport you in this cooler.
嘿  谁在那里
Hey! Who's there!
快点  把我藏起来  我不能被别人看见
Quick! Hide me! My kind must not be seen!
梅宝  今晚还有谁没闯到泳池里
Mabel? Is there anyone not breaking into the pool tonight?
怎么  苏斯不会也在吧
What, is Soos here too?
我还好
I'm okay.
苏斯  回家去
Go home, Soos.
听你的
You got it.
那  你为什么会在这里
So, why are you here?
没有理由啊
Uh, no reason.
那个冷藏箱刚刚是在清嗓子吗
Did that cooler just clear its throat?
别说傻话  这里面当然不会
Don't be silly. There certainly isn't
藏着一条人鱼  如果你想表达这个意思
a merman in there, if that's what you're implying.
有人说什么关于人鱼的东西了吗
Who said anything about a merman?
梅宝  我没空和你玩游戏
Mabel, I don't have time for your games.
如果你不还给我那些东西
If you don't give me those supplies,
我会丢掉有史以来最酷的工作
I'll lose the coolest job ever!
我明白
I understand.
嘿  看啊  穿比基尼的温蒂
Hey, look! Wendy in a bikini!
真的么  这么晚
Really? At night?
抱歉了  迪普
Sorry, Dipper!
梅宝
Mabel!
快走  梅宝  快走
Go, Mabel, go!
我们不可能都得救
We can't all be saved.
我这就送你回家
I'm gonna get you home!
我依泳池规章之名  喝令你归还泳池公物
Hand over the pool supplies in the name of pool law!
泳池规章太傻了  你那顶帽子也一样
Pool law is dumb! And so is your hat!
快看  重力泉湖
Look! Gravity Falls lake!
危险已过
The coast is clear.
我现在只需要在这儿等十五个小时
Now all I have to do is wait here 15 hours
直到泳池开放
Until the pool opens.
真是个好计划
This was a good plan.
我感觉刚刚有人超速了
I think someone just sped by.
可能只是个梦
Probably just a dream.
和你在一起  每天都像梦一样
With you, every day is a dream.
我没法呼吸了
I cannot breathe!
你得快一点
You must hurry!
我还好
I'm okay.
好了  闹够了吧  把冷藏箱还给我
All right, the jig is up! Hand over that cooler!
不行
Never!
为什么  你怎么可能用得到它
Why not? Why do you even need it?
我要用这个冷藏箱拯救我的新朋友
I needed the cooler to save my new friend
因为他需要回家并且他超棒
because he needs to go home and he's really nice.
而且我们互相梳了头发
And we combed each others' hair.
而且他需要待在这个冷藏箱里因为他只能在水里呼吸
And he needs to be in the cooler because he breathes water
因为他是条人鱼
because he's a merman!
你好
Hola.
藏得很深啊  梅宝
Whoa! Way to bury the lead, Mabel.
迪普  这位是美男鱼  他是条人鱼
Dipper, Mermando the merman. He's a merman.
很高兴见到你  另外  我感觉我要死了
Nice to meet you! Also, I think I am dying.
水
Water!
水  我需要水
Agua! Yo necesito!
不要啊  美男鱼
Oh, no! Mermando!
迪普  你是救生员  给他做人工呼吸
Dipper, you're a lifeguard! Give him CPR!
人鱼根本不呼吸空气
Mermen don't breathe air!
那就做反向人工呼吸啊  死脑筋
Then give him reverse CPR! Doi!
我讨厌这种事
I hate this!
你完了
Blackmail!
感谢你救了我
Thank you for saving me,
但你为什么不直接把我扔进湖里
But why didn't you just roll me into the lake?
咳嗽使我变得虚弱
I am weak from coughing.
怎么才能让我的家人从
How will I get my family to hear my call
浩瀚深海里听到我的呼唤
From the mighty depths of the ocean?
我有办法  马上回来
I've got it. B.R.B.
问题解决了
Problem solved!
梅宝  这是泳池公物  我会被解雇的
Mabel, those are pool supplies. I'll get fired!
迪普  你不知道死心塌地爱上某人的感觉吗
Dipper! Don't you know what it's like to fall for someone,
即使在心底你知道
Even though you know in
这段感情可能根本不会有结果
your heart that it'll probably never work out?
但是你依旧会为那个人赴汤蹈火
But you'd do anything for that person?
把扩音器给美男鱼
Give Mermando the megaphone.
谢谢  迪普
Thanks, Dip.
梅宝  我从来没遇见过像你一样的人
Mabel, I have never met anyone like you.
我也是
Same here.
除了见过一个僵尸  一个矮人  和几个可爱的吸血鬼
Except for a zombie, a gnome, and a couple of cute vampires.
我不记得见过吸血鬼
I don't remember the vampires.
我不是什么都和你说的
I don't tell you everything.
好啦  美男鱼  看来该分别了
Well, Mermando, I guess this is it.
还不到  这才是
Not quite. This is!
好吧  太恶心了  啊
Whoa! Okay, that's gross. Ugh.
这是我的初吻
That was my first kiss!
嘿  刚刚也差不多是你的初吻了  是吧
Hey, it was also kind of your first kiss too, huh? Huh?
拜托  别把我卷进来
Please don't involve me in this.
再见  美男鱼
Goodbye, Mermando.
再见  梅宝
Goodbye, Mabel.
你做的是对的  迪普
You did the right thing, Dipper.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah.
等一下  还有一件事
Oh, wait, wait! One last thing!
太好啦
Yes!
我一直都想这么做
I've always wanted to do that.
毁了护栏  刮伤泳池的电瓶车
A wrecked fence, dents in the pool mobile,
还丢了一个扩音器
And a missing megaphone?
谁该为这事负责
Who is responsible for this?!
是我的错  先生  很抱歉  我做得太过分了
It's my fault, sir. I'm sorry. I got in too deep.
把哨子交上来  小子
Hand over the whistle, boy!
如果今天再有一件事出差错
If one more thing goes wrong today...
你们自由啦  自由啦
You're free now! Free!
充气鸭团结起来吧
Inflatable ducks unite!
你
You!
抓住他  抓住他
Git 'em! Git 'em!
嗨  小笨蛋  你绝对猜不到发生了什么
Hey, doofus, you'll never guess what happened.
我刚刚被解雇了
I just got fired.
-什么  真的吗  -是啊
-What? Really? -Yeah.
我猜普切克发现我拿了太多的零食
I guess Poolcheck found out I was taking too many snacks.
有多少
How many?
嘿  想去别的地方破规矩吗
Hey, wanna go break rules somewhere else?
当然
Of course!
亲爱的梅宝  我到家了  和我的家人在一起
"Dear Mabel, I am home with my family,
我非常高兴
And I am very happy..."
我们的初吻我会永远铭记在心
Our first kiss will always hold a place in my heart.
理论上来说  是很多心
Technically hearts...
作为人鱼  我差不多有十七颗心脏
As a merman I have, like, 17 hearts.
很可怕不过是真的
Horrifying but true!
还有更多的瓶子要来
More bottles on the way!
斯坦福
Stanford!
好吧  你赢了  来握个手
Well, guess you've won. Put 'er there.
嘿  这是怎么了
Hey! What the--
除非我预测到了你的计划
Unless perhaps I predicted your plan,
而且昨晚把整个椅子都涂上了胶水
And coated the entire chair with glue last night!
享用你的椅子吧  永远
Enjoy your chair... forever.
孩子们  去拿铲刀  孩子们
Kids, get the spatulas! Kids!